Part Time Pal is a animation, comedy film directed by William Hanna.
Tom is given the task of guarding the fridge during the night by Mammy-Two-Shoes, but as soon as he has
started he is tricked by Jerry into falling into the basement, where he lands in a barrel of cider.
Now drunk, Tom staggers around in the house getting up to no good with Jerry.
Mammy Two-Shoes (voice) (uncredited), played by Lillian Randolph.
Tom (voice) (uncredited), played by Harry Lang.
Tubby the Tuba is a 1947 American animated short film from Paramount
Pictures, directed by George Pal as part of his Puppetoons series.
It was based on the original song by Paul Tripp and George Kleinsinger.
The film features narration by Victor Jory.
The film received an Academy Award nomination for Best
Animated Short, but lost to Warner Bros.
Cartoons' Merrie Melodies cartoon Tweetie Pie.
A feature-length version was released in 1975 by AVCO Embassy.
The 1987 compilation feature, The Puppetoon Movie,
featured the original short in its entirety.
The film explores themes of cartoon cat, cartoon mouse, intoxication.
The tone is lighthearted.